# Michael Hageali

1895 S. Morrison Ln. Gilbert, Arizona (480)457-9981 zmanphx2000@yahoo.com

## **Summary**

Motivated, analytical software developer /programmer. Experienced custom programming in .NET Visual Studio, C#, VB, Java, Java Script HTML with SQL databases, web api, Ajax, jquery and Bootstrap, Node js, NPM, MVC, React, MongoDB, RESTful API. I have worked in Healthcare Industry on software development side primarily with HL7 (EDI), database projects. Open to any new position utilizing my experience and skill set. Willing to relocate if needed.

## **Skills and Certification Training**

- C#, VB, Java, HTML, Java Script, .Net programming Visual Studio, CSS, Bootstrap
- SQL Database, T-SQL, MySQL, Stored Procedures scripting, Node Js, MVC, REST API
- HL7 (EDI) development
- TCP/IP Communications
- SQL Data extraction and integration
- Visual Studio Team Management Source Control
- QA testing and planning
- Software design and logic flow
- Technical Solutions Requirements Analysis
- TFS, Git hub

## Web Full -Stack Experience

The past 6 months I have been in certification training for full-stack development. The training program includes assignments and projects utilizing HTML, CSS, Java Script, Visual Studio Code, Git, , NPM , Node Js., MVC , REST API, Ajax, MySql, Mongo DB, React, Bootstrap, ES6 . My GitHub repository is : <a href="https://github.com/zmanphx">https://github.com/zmanphx</a> .

## **Employment History**

LVM Systems

Data Team Integrator/ .Net Developer SQL Mesa, Arizona

February 2015 – October 2018

- Custom programming solutions for C# .Net SQL database . Project integration developer , solutions analyst. Teams based using Team Foundation Server (TFS)
- Code reports for records migration .Net/ SQL scripting.
- Client support to trouble- shoot transaction exception issues.
- Help train junior level employees with code scripting. QA testing and debug code in .NET.

**Environment**: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, API, C#, SQL, Visual Studio, TFS

#### McKesson Health

Client Support Engineer / .Net developer SQL

Scottsdale, Arizona

June 2001 – February 2015

- Provided analysis for technical solution based on client requirements
- Customized C# programming, installation, and support of client site data interfaces.
- Coded HL7 to sites: Epic, Cerner, Star, Touchworks, All Scripts
- Stored procedures development in **SQL**.
- Project management for customer sites for new software development. Have multiple roles as analyst, developer, QA management, deployment
- Provided consultative services on technical issues to clients and internal project teams. Installations.
- Provided training for operations personal on their support roles.
- Code TCP/IP and HL7 protocols.
- Troubleshooted technical and data issues

### Schaller Anderson (Medicare Billing)

Report Writer, developer

Phoenix, Arizona

October 1999 – June 2001

- Key Responsibilities: Custom report writing in Crystal Reports to report medical billing statistics.
- SQL database programming
- Created Disease Management statistical reporting

#### **World Com Wireless**

Contractor programmer

Phoenix, Arizona

January 1998 – October 1999

- Program database logic for wireless billing for monthly promotions.
- Import wireless record plans using custom coding.

#### MicroAge

Catalog developer

August 1995 – December 1997

- Custom developer of CD-ROM product catalog for computer hardware for VAR vendors.
- Produce monthly catalogs with updated pricing.
- Code pricing algorithm key for each VAR vendor

### **Education**

### **University of Arizona**

Full Stack Development -Certification Program (currently enrolled 2019). Certification Training with tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, web api, Postman, Firebase, Node.js, NPM, Ajax. Web API, RESTful API, MVC, MySQL

### **Brigham Young University**

Bachelor's Degree , Information technology, database design Business degree with emphasis on information technology and System Development Life Cycle and coding development.